# Mehmet Orkun Alabaz

 Istanbul, Turkey
 ■ oalabaz@gmail.com
 □ +905551599099
 Inhttps://www.linkedin.com/in/oalabaz/
 ■ https://orqon.com

#### **SUMMARY**

Fullstack Developer at Firefly with 11 years of experience in all aspects of software development. Expertise in front-end and back-end development for web and mobile applications. Proven understanding of clean code, full-stack development, and testing. Seeking a role as a full-stack developer.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Fullstack Developer**

**Firefly** 

January 2019 - Present, San Francisco, CA

- Reviewed and analyzed code for API's and web applications, built complex web applications that were responsive, SEO optimized and easy to use, with complex backend and frontend features.
- · Designed, developed and maintained a large scale web application using node, express, react.

# **Fullstack Developer**

groupon.com

January 2010 - May 2014, Chicago

- · Designed and developed a robust and scalable system for managing and analyzing our data, according to our needs.
- · Grew a JavaScript and AngularJS PWA app into a fully-functioning SaaS app, including handling users' data, storing and updating

#### **Fullstack Developer**

Vodafone

May 2006 - May 2011, london

 $\cdot \ Analyzed \ and \ improved \ product \ roadmap, \ key \ performance \ indicators \ and \ competitive \ benchmarks \ through \ the \ creation \ of \ an \ enterprise \ ready \ CRM \ platform.$ 

## **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Information Technologies** 

Minor in Information Technologies · UCLA · Los Angeles, CA · 2001

### **SKILLS**

Soft Skills: React, Nodejs, Javascript, Js, Bootstrap, Css, Html, Json, Bootstrap, Nodejs, React Redux, Frontend, Angular React, Reactjs Angularjs, Reactjs Vuejs, Graphql Apollo, Socket Io, Opengl